Guide to the Henry Knox Sherrill Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Biographical Documentation, 1900-1986; Series III
  - Oversize Scrapbooks
    - Volume 4 -- Election as Presiding Bishop through ceremonies and consecration of Bishop Nash, 1946-1947 (Box Ov21)
    - Volume 5 -- Lambeth Conference; World Council of Churches, Amsterdam, 1948 (Box Ov22)
    - Volume 6 -- 56th General Convention, San Francisco, 1949 (Box Ov22)
    - Volume 7 -- Trip to the Far East, 1953 (Box Ov23)
    - Volume 8 -- Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box Ov23)
    - Volume 9 -- Miscellaneous, 1956 Mar - 1957 Sep (Box Ov24)
    - Volume 10 -- Lambeth Conference, 1958 (Box Ov25)
    - Volume 11 -- Episcopal Church Foundation Dinner, 1965 (Box Ov26)
    - Volume 12 -- Miscellaneous, 1946-1980 (Box Ov26)
- Subject File, 1832-1978; Series IV
  This Series is arranged alphabetically by topic. Dates for the material are provided as available. An oversize card file completes the series.
  - Ault, Bromwell, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 601)
  - Brooks, Phillips, 1861-1942, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 602)
  - Davis, Champion, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 603)
  - Day, Gardiner, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 603)
  - Episcopal Church Foundation, 1949-1957 (Box 30, Folder 604)
  - Episcopal Church Foundation, 1965-1972 (Box 30, Folder 605)
  - Episcopal Church Foundation, 1974-1977, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 606)
  - Episcopal Theological School, Cambridge, 1962-1967, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 607)
  - Ferris, Theodore Parker, 1947-1977 (Box 30, Folder 608)
  - Fisher, Geoffrey Francis, 1950-1955 (Box 30, Folder 609)
  - Fisher, Geoffrey Francis, 1958-1978, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 610-613)
  - Good Samaritan, Inc., 1945-1975 (Box 31, Folder 614)
  - Greek Orthodox Church, 1957-1965 (Box 31, Folder 614A)
  - Grenfell, Wilfred, 1938-1963, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 615)
  - Harvard University, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 616)
  - Hobson, Henry, 1955-1975 (Box 31, Folder 616A)
  - Hotchkiss School, 1962, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 617)
  - Knox, Zeba, 1868 (Box 31, Folder 618)
  - Lawrence, William, 1919-1972, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 619)
  - Mann, Alexander, 1919-1923 (Box 31, Folder 620)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital Committee on Research, Subcommittee on Human Studies, 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder 621)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital 150th Anniversary, 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 622)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital: Reports, appeals, 1944-1968 (Box 31, Folder 623-624)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital: Reports, appeals, 1969-1972, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 625)
  - National Council of Churches Formation, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 626-627)
  - National Council of Churches, 25th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 628)
  - National Council of Churches, misc., 1952-1957, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 629)
  - Niemoller, Martin, 1947, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 630)
  - Person, Matilda, 1889-1944 (Box 32, Folder 630)
  - Prayer Book controversy, 1973, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 631)
  - Presiding Bishop, Office of, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 631A)
  - St. Mark's School, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 632)
  - Seabury House, 1947-1957 (Box 32, Folder 633)
  - Seabury House, 1958-1974, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 634)
  - Sherrill, Franklin Goldthwaite, 1927, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 635)
  - Sherrill, Henry W. and Maria Knox, 1900-1901, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 636)
  - Sherrill House, Boston, 1969-1970, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 637)
  - Society of the Cincinnati, 1949-1976 (Box 32, Folder 638)
  - Sturges, Philemon, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 639)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 639)
  - Thayer, Captain Oliver, 1832 (Box 32, Folder 639)
  - Trinity Church, Boston, 1933, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 640)
  - Tyler, Samuel, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 641)
  - Whitehill, Walter Muir, 1975, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 641)
  - World Council of Churches, 1948-1968, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 642)
  - World War II miscellany, 1943-1945, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 643-644)
  - Yale University, 1937-1963 (Box 33, Folder 645)
  - Yashiro, Michael, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 646)
  - Oversize Card file compiled by HKS listing individuals and organizations, alphabetically
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1885-1968, n.d.; Series V
  - Artifacts
    Three inkwells originally listed for the collection are no longer available (itemss 4,5,8)
    - 1. Brass boat wall plaque, inscribed: NCCC, 1950-1952 (Box Ov1)
    - 2. Wooden paddle from Yale (Box Ov1)
    - 3. Russian icon given to HKS at his consecration by Bishop of Massachusetts (Box Ov1)
    - 6. Silver tray for inkwells from Church's chaplains of World War II (Box Ov1)
    - 7. Silver letter opener, inscribed: H.K.S. from W.L. May, 1930 (Box Ov2)
    - 9. Silver notepaper holder (Box Ov2)
    - 10. Small tapestry of ornate material (Box Ov2)
    - 11. Leather manuscript case, stamped: H.K.S. from J.T.A. and M.C.A. (Box Ov2)
    - 12. Brass medal from World Council of Churches Second Assembly, 1954 (Box Ov2)
    - 13. Brass medal from Army and Navy Commission of Protestant Episcopal Church, 1941-1945 (Box Ov2)
    - 14. Brass medal from Princeton University (Box Ov2)
    - 15. Medal from Protestant Episcopal Church, 58th General Convention (Box Ov2)
    - 16. Letter clip, inscribed: "From Young People's Fellowship of Trinity Church" (Box Ov2)
    - 17. Calendar adjustable to any year, in engraved metal frame (Box Ov2)
    - 18. Silver medal for service to Yale, 1960 (Box Ov2)
    - 19. Silver plaque - -- "Le Vetement du Prisonnier de Guerre. Fonde Decembre 1914." (Box Ov2)
    - 20. Carved mother of pearl pendant with painted Madonna and child (Box Ov3)
    - 21. Carved ivory cross with inset gems (Box Ov3)
    - 22. Grey stone cross with three-link stone chain (Box Ov3)
    - 23. Gold cross, inscribed: June 24, 1956 (Box Ov3)
    - 24. Small ivory cross with blue and rose gems inlaid (Box Ov3)
    - 25. Gold charm of torch (Box Ov3)
    - 26. Gold and enamel charm, inscribed: "Vinces in Hoc Signo" (Box Ov3)
    - 27. Brass medal awarded to chaplains of American Army and Navy, 1917-1918 (Box Ov3)
    - 28. Pin bought by Franklin Goldthwaite Sherrill, 1885 (Box Ov3)
    - 29. Holy Cross from Alexis, Patriarch of Russia, 1956 (Box Ov3)
    - 30. Greek Cross awarded to HKS, 1946 (Box Ov4)
    - 31. United States Merit Medal (Box Ov4)
    - 32. French honor medal (Honneur et Patrie) (Box Ov4)
  - Books
    - 1. History of Base Hospital No. 6, U.S. Army, 1924 (Box Ov5)
    - 2. Bible used by HKS at his consecration as Bishop of Massachusetts, 1930 (Box Ov5)
    - 3. Installation service as Presiding Bishop, January 14, 1947 (Box Ov5)
    - 4. Report of the President's Committee on Civil Rights, 1947 (Box Ov5)
    - 5. Elizabeth II's Coronation Service, June 2, 1953 (Box Ov5)
    - 6. St. Mark's Looks Forward: Published on the occasion of St. Mark's School's 100th Anniversary (Box Ov5)
    - 7. Selected sermons of Theodore P. Ferris (Box Ov5)
    - 8. Leather bound New Testament (Box Ov5)
    - 9. The Scottish Book of Common Prayer, 1929: notes on its origin and growth, by Alan Campbell Don (Box Ov5)
    - 10. The Interchurch Center: Reminiscences of an Incorrigible Promoter, by Francis Stuart Harmon (Box Ov5)
    - 11. Guest book: Dover House, Greenwich, Connecticut (Box Ov4)
  - B1. Books belonging to BHS
    - 1. Diary (Box Ov4)
    - 2. The Fiancee's Book (listing of shower gifts, special parties, etc.) (Box Ov4)
    - 3. Wedding Gifts (Box Ov4)
  - C. Phonograph records
    - 1. Recording of speeches made at "Sherrill Dinner", October 14, 1958 (Box Ov15)
    - 2. General Convention of the Protestant Episcopal Church, Boston, September, 1952 (Box Ov15)
    - 3. Highlights from dinner in honor of Yale's crew and football teams, February 13, 1957 (Box Ov15)
    - 4. Address of President Griswold to members of Yale's Program for the Arts and Sciences, April 12, 1962 (Box Ov15)
    - 5. "Builders for Christ" including address by HKS (Box Ov15)
    - 6. Episcopal Church special broadcast of HKS and Trinity Church choir (Box Ov15)
    - 7. Episcopal Church special broadcast, February 29, 1948 (Box Ov15)
  - D. Academic hoods
    - 1. Yale L.L.D. (Box Ov6)
    - 2. Berkeley Divinity School D.D., 1954 (Box Ov6)
    - 3. Two unidentified hoods (both black and red) (Box Ov6)
    - 4. Boston College L.L.D., 1930 (Box Ov6)
    - 5. Unidentified hood (black, yellow, and red) (Box Ov6)
    - 6. Philadelphia Divinity School D.D., 1947 (Box Ov7)
    - 7. Episcopal Theological School D.D. (Box Ov7)
    - 8. General Theological Seminary S.T.D. (Box Ov7)
    - 9. From Lambeth Conference, 1958 (Box Ov7)
    - 10. Berkeley (Box Ov7)
    - 11. Hobart College D.D., 1948 (Box Ov8)
    - 12. University of Tennessee, 1957 (Box Ov8)
    - 13. Yale D.D., 1929 (Box Ov8)
    - 14. Norwich University D.Lit., 1952 (Box Ov8)
    - 15. University of Rochester D.D., 1951 (Box Ov8)
    - 16. Unidentified hood (red, black, light blue, white) (Box Ov9)
    - 17. Unidentified hood (red, black, navy, tan) (Box Ov9)
    - 18. Trinity College D.D., 1936 (Box Ov9)
    - 19. University of Idaho (Box Ov9)
    - 20. Union College D.Cn.L., 1952 (Box Ov10)
    - 21. Princeton University D.D., 1947 (Box Ov10)
    - 22. Lehigh University L.L.D. (Box Ov10)
  - E. Citations, degrees, diplomas
    - 1. Diploma from Polytechnic Preparatory School, 1906 (Box Ov16)
    - 2. Diploma from Hotchkiss School, 1907 (Box Ov16)
    - 3. Diploma from Yale University, 1911
    - 4,5. Certificates of appointment as chaplain, 1916, 1918 (Box Ov11)
    - 6. Certificate of appointment as Rector of the Church of Our Saviour, Brookline, 1919 (Box Ov11)
    - 7. Certificate of appointment as Rector of Trinity Church, Boston, 1923 (Box Ov11)
    - 8. Petition from diocese of Pennsylvania, 1929
    - 9. Honorary D.D., Yale University, 1929
    - 10. Honorary S.T.D., Trinity College, 1936 (Box Ov11)
    - 11. Honorary S.T.D., Harvard University, 1936 (Box Ov11)
    - 12,13. Certifications of election as Presiding Bishop, 1946
    - 14. Honorary L.L.D., Lehigh University, 1946 (Box Ov11)
    - 15. Certificate of appreciation from the Navy to Mrs. Sherrill, 1946 (Box Ov11)
    - 16. Diploma awarded by Serbian Orthodox Church, 1947 (Box Ov11)
    - 17. Honorary D.D., Princeton University, 1947 (Box Ov11)
    - 18. Honorary S.T.D, Philadelphia Divinity School, 1947
    - 19. Citation from the Navy, 1947 (Box Ov11)
    - 20. Honorary S.T.D., General Theological Seminary, 1947 (Box Ov13)
    - 21. Honorary S.T.D., Columbia University, 1948 (Box Ov13)
    - 22. Honorary S.T.D., Seabury-Western Theological Seminary, 1949 (Box Ov13)
    - 23,24. Honorary D.D., University of Edinburgh, 1949 (Box Ov13)
    - 25. Honorary D.D., University of Rochester, 1951 (Box Ov13)
    - 26. Honorary D.D., University of Denver, 1952 (Box Ov13)
    - 27. Honorary D.C.L., Union College, 1952 (Box Ov13)
    - 28. Honorary Th.D., Russian Orthodox Theological Academy, Paris, 1952 (Box Ov13)
    - 29. Honorary D.D., Hamilton College, 1953 (Box Ov13)
    - 30. Honorary D.Lit., Norwich University, 1954 (Box Ov13)
    - 31. Honorary S.T.D., Berkeley Divinity School, 1954 (Box Ov13)
    - 32. Honorary D.D., College of Idaho, 1956 (Box Ov13)
    - 33. Honorary D.C.L., University of the South, 1957 (Box Ov13)
    - 34. Citation from the Legion of Honor, 1958 (Box Ov13)
    - 35. Honorary L.L.D., Yale University, 1960 (Box Ov13)
    - 36. Honorary D.D. from Archbishop of Canterbury, 1958
    - 37. Citation from the Protestant Episcopal Church for ecumenical service, 1961 (Box Ov14)
    - 38,39. Honorary D.D., Episcopal Theological School, 1961 (Box Ov14)
    - 40. Certificate of election to the Massachusetts Historical Society, 1968 (Box Ov14)
    - 41. Certificate of ordination to the priesthood (Box Ov14)
    - 42. Citation from Episcopalian Club of Massachusetts, 1946 (Box Ov12)
    - 43. Citation from All Saints Episcopal Church, 1941 (Box Ov12)
    - 44. Citation from Colored Citizens of Boston, 1947 (Box Ov12)
    - 45. Citation from N.A.A.C.P. (Box Ov12)
    - 46. Citation from St. Christopher's Guild, Trinity Church
    - 47. Honorary D.D., Hobart and William Smith College, 1948 (Box Ov14)
- Photographs, 1891-1978, n.d.; Series VI
  - Portraits of HKS
    - Portraits, ca. 1891-1930 (Box 34, Folder 647)
    - Portraits, 1954, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 648)
  - Portraits of Family Members
    - Parents, brother (Box 34, Folder 649)
    - Wife, children, grandchildren, great-grandchildren (Box 34, Folder 650)
  - Chronological Sequence
    - Photographs, 1930-1978, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 651-659)
  - Oversize Photographs and Photograph Albums
    - 1. Album--re: Episcopal 57th General Convention, visit of Geoffrey Fisher, etc.
    - 2. Album -- primarily portraits
    - 3. Album -- re: World Council of Churches
    - 4. Album -- re: National Council of Churches delegation to Russia, 1956 (Box Ov17)
    - 5. Portrait of F. D. Maurice (Box Ov17)
    - 6. Archbishop and Mrs. Fisher and company (Box Ov17)
    - 7. Time Magazine portrait of HKS, March 25, 1951
    - 8. HKS ordination service (Box Ov17)
    - 9,9a. HKS consecration service, 1930 (Box Ov17)
    - 10. Bishops in procession at HKS's consecration as Bishop of Massachusetts, 1930 (2 copies) (Box Ov17)
    - 11. HKS and chaplains ln Rome, 1945 (Box Ov17)
    - 12. HKS and General Patton, 1945 (Box Ov17)
    - 13. The Bishop's Laymen Division Dinner, Boston, 1946 (Box Ov17)
    - 14. Lambeth Conference, 1948
    - 15. Lambeth Conference, 1948
    - 16. Lambeth Conference, 1958
    - 17. Service during House of Bishops meeting (Box Ov18)
    - 18. 51st General Convention, House of Bishops, Atlantic City (Box Ov18)
    - 19. 50th reunion of Calhoun College, class of 1911 (Box Ov18)
    - 20. Collection of photographs taken of a play in which HKS played a woman, Millicent
    - 21. Unidentified photo of a play or musical cast (Box Ov18)
    - 22. Unidentified group portrait: men before Osborn Hall
    - 23. Same as # 22
    - 24. Unidentified clans portrait (Box Ov18)
    - 25. Unidentified group of young men (Box Ov18)
    - 26. Framed photo of enthronement of Geoffrey Cantuar (Box Ov18)
    - 27. Framed photo of World Council of Churches presidents (Box Ov18)
    - 28. Portraits of EKS as Bishop of Brazil, 1983 (Box Ov19)
    - 29. Postcards and loose photos (Box Ov19)
    - 30. Postcards and loose photos (Box Ov19)
    - 31. Album - primarily Prue and family (Box Ov19)
    - 32. Family album (Box Ov19)
- Addendum - 2009, 1859-2003, n.d.; Series VII
  - Family Correspondence
    The first folder contains a detailed inventory of documents and photographs contained in the addendum, prepared by Rebecca Sherrill More (granddaughter of Henry Knox Sherrill and daughter of Henry Williams Sherrill)
    - Early family letters
      - Henry W. Sherrill (father of HKS) to his father Rev. Franklin G. Sherrill, 1883 Jul (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Mariana Margati (mother of Barbara Harris Sherrill) to family, 1888 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Henry W. Sherrill (father of HKS) to his brother Gus Sherrill, 1891 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Henry Knox Sherrill and Barbara Harris Sherrill
      - HKS to Barbara Harris (Sherrill), 1921 May (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - From mother of BHS, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - BHS to children, 1948-1961 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - HKS to children, 1933-1956 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - From children, 1948-1954 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Henry Williams Sherrill (son of HKS)
      - Letters to/from his parents while at Yale, including telegram re. "tap" for Scroll & Key society, 1942-1947 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Letters from his parents, 1948-1958 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Including postcards from brother Goldthwaite, to/from brother Edmund, 1933, 1969-1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence
    - Henry Knox Sherrill
      - Including from T.M. Griffiths, Sinclair Weeks, 1936, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Henry Williams Sherrill
      - A - B, including to/from R. Achs, M. Arnold, M. Baker, S. Bayne, Kingman Brewster, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - C - D, including to/from P. Chappell, H. Collins, M. Coombs, L. Davis, S. DeVaux, 1969, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - G - M, including to/from M. Gibbs, J. Hanley, J. Johnston, M. Levine, John. V. Lindsay, 1966-1969 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - O - S, including to/from J. Ordway, W. Reding, J. Shetterley, W. Stuhr; H. W. Sherrill family circulars (1991,1992), 1969-1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - T - W, including to/from W. Taylor, S. Weeks, P. Whittemore, G. Workman (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Others
      - Robert Greenleaf to Karl Menninger, unidentified, 1959, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Writings, Sermons, Notes
    - Henry Williams Sherrill
      - Sermons and speeches including Easter telecast, "The King Nobody Wanted", "Christmas - with Light", etc. (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Sermons and speeches including "The Holy Bible - a Guide for Leaders and Decision Makers", etc. (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Notes - meditations (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Notebook of notes (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Notes from trips to England an California, 1982, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Writings of others
      - Copies of brief works by Oliver Thayer, handwritten poem, 1887, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Biographical Documentation
    - Henry Knox Sherrill
    - Newspapers clippings, magazine articles, tribute booklet re. HKS, 1946-1970, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Henry Williams Sherrill
      - Baptism certificate, birth certificate copies, report cards from Longwood Day School, Milton Academy, Milton Academy award of athletic letter and diploma, 1922-1958 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Handwritten childhood speeches on Benjamin Franklin, John Paul Jones (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - U.S. Army induction and discharge papers, 1943-1946 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Yale College commencement program, diploma, certificate from Timothy Dwight College; grade report from Union Theological Seminary, certificate of clinical training, 1947-1949 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Re. churches served in Michigan and Ohio, 1953-1955, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Certificate and photo re. visit to Strategic Air Command, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Articles re. appointment as Executive Officer of Diocese of Southern Ohio, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Notebooks and documents related to HWK trip to Brazil, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Reunion books for Milton Academy and Yale University, 1991, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 28)
      - HWS Obituaries, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Collected Items
      - Writings related to psychology and religion by Paul Tillich, John Ordway, unidentified, 1960, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 30)
      - Materials related to MGH Institute of Health Professions, incl. regarding Henry Knox Sherrill Professorship and Lecture in Ethics. (Massachusetts General Hospital), 1983, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 31)
      - Document re. by-laws of Good Samaritan, Inc., 1999 (Box 45, Folder 31)
      - Newspaper clippings, magazine articles and church programs (Box 45, Folder 32-33)
    - Photographs
      - Early family photos: H.W. Sherrill I, Thayer-Margati family, Jose Calderon Margati de Roco (grandfather of Barbara Harris Sherrill), 1859-1880s (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - Portraits of Henry Knox Sherrill, 1893-1959 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - H. K. and Barbara Sherrill, 1950s-1975 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Group/work photos of H.K. Sherrill, 1950s, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Misc. Sherrill family photos, incl. visit to Sherrill family graves, Louisville, KS, 1927-1999 (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - Portraits of Henry Williams Sherrill, 1933-1999 (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - H. W. Sherrill school activities: Longwood Day School, Milton Academy, Yale College, incl. Yale baseball and swimming teams, Yale University Undergraduate Board of Deacons, 1933-1947 (Box 45, Folder 37)
      - H.W. Sherrill group and work-related photos, 1950s (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Addendum - 2016, 1955-2015
  An annotated inventory of the addendum, prepared by its donor, Rebecca Weeks Sherrill More, is available in Box 46, Folder 1.
  - Family correspondence
    - Henry Knox Sherrill to eldest grandchild, Rebecca Weeks Sherrill (More): postcards, 1955-1958 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Henry Knox Sherrill (HKS) and Barbara Harris Sherrill (BHS) to/from granddaughter Rebecca (RWSM), 1959-1961 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1962-1964 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, circular letter from Archbishop Geoffrey Fisher, 1970-1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - HKS and BHS to RWSM, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - BHS to RWSM, 1977-1983 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Biographical documentation
    - Henry Knox Sherrill: newspaper articles, 1970-1977 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Henry Knox Sherrill: Memorial service program, tributes, announcement of Henry Knox Sherrill Symposium on Ethics, Massachusetts General Hospital, 1980-1983 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Henry Williams Sherrill: letters of tribute and concern at time of his final illness and death, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Henry Williams Sherrill: related to memorial service, tributes, sketch of HWS in 1955, history of Cheswick Center describing impact of HWS as founder, 1991-2001 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Franklin Goldthwaite Sherrill, II: memorial service, tributes, 2015 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Edmund Knox Sherrill; memorial services programs, tribute (2015), memorial service for death of daughter Mary Sherrill Forrester (2004), 2004-2015 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Barbara Prue Sherrill Wilson: circular letters, photographs, 1987-2000 (Box 46, Folder 18)